trex.com 2019-12-06

# Privacy Policy | Trex

## Trex Privacy Policy

Trex Company, Inc. ("Trex") respects your privacy and strives to help you protect your personal information. This Privacy Policy is intended to explain how Trex uses the information you provide to us and with whom it may be shared.

###### Your Consent

By using our website and specifically by filling out one of the Trex online forms or tools, you agree to our collection and use of your personal information as is described in this Privacy Policy. If we change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this website. This Privacy Policy was last updated May 1, 2019.

###### The Type of Information We May Collect

"Personal Information" in this Privacy Policy refers to information that may be used to identify you, such as your name, address, or email address. Personal Information in some jurisdictions can include additional information that indirectly identifies a person absent other identifying information. We will only process Personal Information in accordance with applicable law and as is explained in this Privacy Policy. If you do not want to provide us this Personal Information, please do not utilize these features on the Trex website. You may provide Personal Information to us in the following ways:

  * _Requests for Information or to join our mailing list._ When you request additional information related to our products, we will request your name and contact information such as email address, street address, and phone number. If you request samples, we may also request payment information from you.
  * _Registering your Trex Warranty._ When you register or process your warranty with us you may be asked to provide information such as your name, street address, phone number and email address.
  * _Expressing an Interest in Employment._ If you choose to apply for employment online, express an interest in employment with us, or express a wish to be notified of future employment openings, you will be required to provide your name, street address, email address, telephone number, and certain additional information. You will also have the opportunity to provide us your resume.
  * _Investor relations._ You may subscribe to our investor relations email alert service to learn when new investor information including earnings releases, financial reports, and SEC filings have been made. If you subscribe, we will require your email address. If you would like investor information mailed to you we may ask that you provide your name, street address, email address, and phone number.
  * _Information we collect about your visit to our website using technology._ When you visit our website, we may also collect indirect technical information about your website visit, including your internet protocol (IP) address, browser type, operating system, computer or mobile device type, or navigation and clickstream information. This technical information is used to help us improve users' experience on our website. Depending on where you access our website from, this technical information may or may not be considered Personal Information. We store this information about your visit to our website in an aggregate anonymized way and do not use it to specifically identify you.
  * _Information we obtain from third parties._ We may enhance information that we collect from you with other information we obtain from third parties or companies affiliated with Trex. When we associate information we obtain from third parties with you, we treat that acquired information the same as if we collected it ourselves and as described in this Privacy Policy, and will not share it with third parties.

###### How We Use the Information You Share with Us

We use the Personal Information you share with us to perform the services and provide the information you request. For example, if you fill out a form requesting more information about Trex, we will use the information you provide us to contact you about Trex products. We may also use information you provide us or technical information we collect to help us improve your experience on our website, or to process a warranty claim.

We may share the information we collect, including your Personal Information, among our affiliates, as well as with third parties that assist us in providing the products or services that you requested or that improve our marketing or administration. This includes companies that provide analytics to us about the use of our website, so that we can evaluate our website and continue to improve its content. Because we operate as part of a global business, the recipients referred to above may be located outside the jurisdiction in which you are located (or in which we provide the services). We have put in place appropriate safeguards in accordance with applicable legal requirements to ensure that data is adequately safeguarded and protected irrespective of the country.

Your information may also be shared with Trex's dealers, distributors or contractors on an aggregated, non-personal basis. When Trex shares such information with dealers, distributors or contractors, it is not traceable to any particular user and will not be used to contact you again.

We will not sell, rent, exchange or share your personal information with any third parties without permission or except as described in this Privacy Policy.

Finally, we also may use or disclose information to third parties such as law enforcement agencies and government authorities when we have a good faith belief that it is necessary in order to protect the legal rights, safety, and security of Trex; to respond to and resolve claims or complaints; to prevent fraud or for risk management purposes; and to comply with or respond to law enforcement or legal process or a request for cooperation by a government or other entity.

###### Lawful Bases for Processing Information

We will only collect and process Personal Information where we have lawful bases. Our lawful bases for processing your information could include where you give us consent (for example: when you sign up for our mailing lists), performance of a contract (for example: when you have registered your Trex warranty with us), and other legitimate interests. These other legitimate interests include but are not limited to complying with laws that apply to Trex and enabling us to administer our business (for example: quality control, consolidated reporting, or customer service).

###### Your Rights Regarding Your Personal Information

Depending on the jurisdiction in which you are located, you may have certain rights with regard to your Personal Information. Trex strives to honor those rights. If you have a request about your data or any concerns about the information you provide to us, please contact us at [customercare@trex.com](mailto:customercare@trex.com) with the attention line "Privacy Request." You may also contact the Data Protection Authority in your country.

_Correcting and/or updating your Personal Information._ If you believe any Personal Information we maintain about you is incorrect or incomplete, you may ask us to correct it.

_Deleting or Restricting your Personal Information._ You can also ask us to erase it, restrict it, or you may tell us if you object to our use of your Personal Information.

_Copies Personal Information._ You may also ask us for a copy of Personal Information we maintain about you. Consistent with legal requirements and limitations, we will comply with reasonable requests to obtain a copy of your Personal Information.

We retain the information you share with us for as long as we need to in order to provide you the services you request. For example, if you register a warranty with Trex, we will keep your Personal Information on file in order to help us process your warranty. We also retain other data generated by you (i.e., data generated when you browse our website) in a depersonalized or aggregated form in order to help us improve users' experience on our website. We may also retain your information for a reasonable period of time for Trex to conduct audits, comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, or other legitimate business interests.

###### Where Your Data May Be Sent

If you are located outside of the United States, we may transfer the personal data you provide to us to the United States. By sharing your data with us, you consent to the transfer of your data to the United States.

###### Chilren's Privacy

We do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 13 without parental consent, unless permitted by law. If we learn that a child under the age of 13 has provided us with personal information, we will delete it in accordance with applicable law.

###### California

California residents are entitled once a year, free of charge, to request and obtain certain information regarding our disclosure, if any, of certain categories of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year. We do not share personal information with third parties for their own direct marketing purposes. California residents who are registered users may also request and obtain removal of content. You may request such removal by emailing us at [customercare@trex.com](mailto:customercare@trex.com). In your request, please provide a description of the material that you want removed and information reasonably sufficient to permit us to locate the material, and include your name, email address and the subject line "California Removal Request" so that we can process your request.

###### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Policy, or about Trex's data privacy practices, please contact us at [customercare@trex.com](mailto:customercare@trex.com). Trex may also be contacted via mail at 160 Exeter Drive, Winchester, Virginia 22603. Please address your mail to "Trex Privacy Program." You may also contact the Data Protection Authority in your country.

###### Cookies Notice

Our Site uses "cookies" to help personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your computer's hard disk, mobile phone or other device by a website server. Cookies do not damage your device. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

Generally, cookies provide convenience and save their time. However, we also use cookies to send you advertisements that may be of interest to you. What cookies does Trex use?

_Stricly necessary cookies_

These cookies are essential to enable you to move around our website and use its features. Without these cookies, services you have asked for cannot be provided. They are deleted when you close the browser.

_Performance cokies_

These cookies collect information in an anonymous form about how visitors use our Site. They allow us to recognize and count the number of visitors and help us understand which pages are the most popular and where visitors spend most of their time.

_Functionality cookies_

These cookies allow our Site to remember choices you make, such as your name, the region you are in or the pages you have viewed. They are used to provide enhanced and more personal features.

If you create an account on our Site, a persistent cookie helps Trex recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal data, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use features that you customized. Persistent cookies will be kept on your device until their expiration or earlier manual deletion.

We may also use your IP address sent to us by your browser to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our Site and to improve the service we offer to you. An IP address is a numeric code that identifies your computer on a network, or in this case, the internet. Your IP address might also be used to gather broad demographic information. We may perform IP lookups to determine which domain you are coming from to more accurately gauge our Users' demographics.

_Targeting or advertising cookies_

These cookies allow us and our advertisers to deliver information more relevant to you and your interests. They are also used to limit the number of times you see an advertisement as well as help measure the effectiveness of advertising campaigns. They remember that you have visited our Site and may help us in serving you.

_Social Media cookies_

These cookies allow you to connect with social media networks such as Instagram and YouTube.

We may combine information from these types of cookies and technologies with information about you from any other source.

_User consent to place cookies_

We assume that you are happy for us to place cookies on your device. Most browsers automatically accept cookies. However, if you, or another user of your device, wish to withdraw your consent at any time, you can accept or decline cookies by modifying your browser setting. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of our services or the websites you visit.

###### Third Party Links and Add-ins

This Privacy Policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information collected by Trex through your interaction with our website. Trex's website may link to, or embed content from, other third party websites such as YouTube. When we link to other websites or embed their content, Trex's privacy practices no longer apply. You should refer to the privacy policy of that third party for information about their privacy policies and cookie practices.
